wholinkstome.com 2014-11-22

# WhoLinksToMe Reputation Management Reimagined

### Last modified: March 6, 2010

Star Nine Ventures, Inc., who provides WhoLinksToMe.com and WhoLinksToMe PRO ("we" "us" "WhoLinksToMe.com" or "WhoLinksToMe PRO"), is a licensee of the TRUSTe Web Privacy Seal Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site www.wholinkstome.com., including any and all free or paid services. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first email Customer Service at [CustomerService@wholinkstome.com](mailto:CustomerService@wholinkstome.com). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php).

Because we understand how important your privacy and security are, WhoLinksToMe.com has provided the following security guidelines for your review so that you will understand how the information you give us is used. 

## Registration 

In order to conduct link research on WhoLinksToMe.com, you must first complete the registration form by providing contact information such as your email address and creating a password. We use the information provided to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest or in which we believe you may have an interest. We utilize the basic demographic information you give us in order to provide a more personalized experience on our site. Star Nine Ventures, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on WhoLinksToMe.com. 

If at any point you need to access your personally identifiable information to correct or update it, please email us at [CustomerService@wholinkstome.com](mailto:CustomerService@wholinkstome.com). 

## Service-related Announcements 

We will send you service-related announcements on occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. 

You may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. 

## Customer Service 

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email. 

## Profile 

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, to create a "profile" of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information to information in the profile in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site. 

## Log Files 

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes, but is not limited to, internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

If you choose to upload your external sources of link data to WhoLinksToMe.com, this information becomes part of our database. This information may be shared with other site users, site applications, other products or services we may offer or for other promotional or commercial purposes. 

## Links to Other Sites 

This website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by WhoLinksToMe.com. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by WhoLinksToMe.com. 

## Blog/Feedback 

If you leave comments on the WhoLinksToMe.com Web site, blog or participate in Feedback or other conversations, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in connection with this use of the Web site. 

## Special Offers and Updates 

We will send you information on products and services that we think may interest you. You can sign up for these emails from us on our registration page. 

Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please feel free to email us at [CustomerService@wholinkstome.com](mailto:CustomerService@wholinkstome.com) to discontinue (opt-out) these messages. 

We may use or share your information internally or with our business partners to better provide you with products and/or services and/or offers, or in connection with other promotional or commercial purposes. 

## Legal Disclaimer 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

## Security 

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

## Changes in this Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here and/or email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

If you have any questions about security on our website, please feel free to contact WhoLinksToMe.com or by emailing [CustomerService@wholinkstome.com](mailto:CustomerService@wholinkstome.com).

Star Nine Ventures, Inc.  
1604 Nueces St.   
Austin Texas, 78701
